room that I work in my
company,
what have we got to know
about them and do to make
sure that they thrive, stay motivated
and achieve their
I don't like the conversations of
strengths and weaknesses because
strengths often have
liability.
really confident. Okay, in the wrong
context you're arrogant. Right?
weaknesses also have several linings.
So for me, I'm chronically disorganized.
I'm terrible. Right?
It's a terrible weakness. But the
reality is it's context. So I
was at this as a young
entrepreneur, I was at this networking
event and
I met this guy who's like
really impressed with what I had
to say with my pitch and
he's like Simon, we have to
do work together. Here's my business
card. Call me. Let's do this.
And I lost the business card
basically as soon as he gave
it to me. So anybody who
was organized would be sending a
text from the taxi or at
least sending an email the next
day. Not Yahoo over here. I
lost the business card. There was
no way for me to find
out what this important piece of
business would have led to that.
Two weeks later, I found the
business card at the bottom of
the briefcase.
So I emailed him and said,
hey, do you remember we met
two weeks ago? You know, I'd
love to reconnect and see if
we can work together still. He
wanted to work with me more
because he thought I was busy.
So strength or weakness, the answer
is it depends. Now, in general,
yes, it is a weakness. It's
a liability and it causes me
great stress.
not always is the point. And
so