How do I as a leader make sure that if I'm hiring Gen Z and I've got a couple even in
this room that work in my company, what have we got to know about them and do to make sure
that they thrive, stay motivated and achieve their goals?
I don't like the conversation of strengths and weaknesses.
I don't like the conversations of strengths and weaknesses because strengths often have
liability.
I'm really confident, okay, in the wrong context you're arrogant, right?
But weaknesses also have silver linings.
So strength or weakness, the answer is it depends.
But not always is the point.
And so, yes, it's important for us to understand our characteristics that we exhibit of which
some of them in certain contexts are huge strengths and some of the exact same characteristics
in the wrong context are huge weaknesses.
So we have to be very careful when we label people or generations as being strong or weak
because the answer is it depends.