Make sure that they thrive, stay motivated,
and achieve their goals.
I don't like the conversations
of strengths and weaknesses,
because strengths often have liabilities.
I'm really confident. In the wrong context, you're arrogant.
Weaknesses also have silver linings.
For me, I'm chronically disorganized.
Every system I try works for a weekend, and I'm back to being disorganized.
Is that a good thing or bad enough
for me to beat myself up for it
and say it's a terrible weakness?
The reality is: it's context.
So strength or weakness?
The answer is: it depends.
Yes, it creates stress,
but that's not always the point.
It's important for us to understand
our characteristics,
because some of those same traits
are huge strengths in certain contexts,
and huge weaknesses in others.
Be careful labeling people or generations as strong or weak, because it depends.
They exhibit many of the same characteristics
as the previous generation,
but they're different in the sense
that they're very activist.