What is the workplace for them?
How do I as a leader make sure that if I'm
hiring Gen Z and I've got a couple even in
this room that work in my company, what
have we got to know about them and do to
make sure
that they thrive, stay motivated and
achieve their goals?
This is my own bias.
I don't like the conversation.
My own bias.
I don't like the conversation of strengths
and weaknesses.
I don't like the conversations of
strengths and weaknesses because strengths
often have
liability.
I'm really confident.
Okay, in the wrong context, you're
arrogant.
Right?
But weaknesses also have silver linings.
Now for years, I used to beat myself up
for it and say it's a bad thing.
It's a terrible weakness.
But the reality is it's context.
And so yes, it's important for us to
understand our characteristics that we
exhibit, of which
some of them in certain contexts are huge
strengths and some of the exact same
characteristics
in the wrong context are huge weaknesses.
So we have to be very careful when we
label people or generations as being
strong or weak
because the answer is it depends.