When you think about helping young people
stay motivated at work,
you have to start with what they actually care about.
It is not just a paycheck.
They want to feel like the work matters,
and that someone notices the effort.
Give them context for the bigger picture
so the small daily tasks feel connected.
Real feedback, in the moment,
is one of the most powerful tools we have.
Don't wait for an annual review
to tell them where they stand.
Show them a path that goes somewhere.
If they cannot see growth, they leave.
Build trust by listening to what's hard,
and acting on what you hear.
Pair them with people who invest in them.
A good mentor changes everything early on.
Celebrate the wins, even the small ones,
because momentum is what keeps people going.
When you do these things consistently,
young people don't just stay — they thrive.