But how do I as a leader make sure that if I'm hiring Gen Zee and I've got a couple
even in this room that I work in my company, what have we got to know about them and do
to make sure that they thrive, stay motivated and achieve their goal?
I don't like the conversations of strengths and weaknesses because strengths often have
liability.
I'm really confident, okay, in the wrong context you're arrogant, right?
But weaknesses also have silver linings.
So for me, I'm chronically disorganized, I'm terrible, right?
Every system works for like a week and then I'm back to being disorganized.
Is that a good thing or a bad thing?
Now for years I used to beat myself up for it and say it's a bad thing, it's a terrible
weakness.
But the reality is, it's context.
So we have to be very careful when we label people or generations as being strong or weak because
the answer is it depends.
When we talk about this young generation, the Gen Z generation?
They exhibit many of the same characteristics as the previous generation but they're quite
different in the sense that they're very activist, right?